{
    "subject": "resource/Guy_Leverne_Fake",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Judges_of_the_United_States_District_Court_for_the_District_of_New_Jersey",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Guy Leverne Fake's work is Judges of the United States District Court for the District of New Jersey.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9573180675506592,
            "question": "Where do the judges that Guy Leverne Fake studies work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9536651968955994,
            "question": "Who are the subjects of Guy Leverne Fake's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8782909512519836,
            "question": "Does Guy Leverne Fake study judges from a particular state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8372653126716614,
            "question": "Is there a specific characteristic or aspect of judges that Guy Leverne Fake investigates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8337555527687073,
            "question": "Can you name the court that Guy Leverne Fake's work covers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8154981732368469,
            "question": "What is Guy Leverne Fake's area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8143279552459717,
            "question": "What level of the judicial system does Guy Leverne Fake's work examine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7361394762992859,
            "question": "Which court system does Guy Leverne Fake focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7305933833122253,
            "question": "What type of legal professional does Guy Leverne Fake's work involve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5989385843276978,
            "question": "What is the specific focus of Guy Leverne Fake's research?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Guy Leverne Fake's work is Judges of the United States District Court for the District of New Jersey.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1367_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of legal professional does Guy Leverne Fake's work involve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1367_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which court system does Guy Leverne Fake focus on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1367_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What level of the judicial system does Guy Leverne Fake's work examine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1367_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1367_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The text does not mention Guy Leverne Fake or his work, let alone mentioning that the subject of his work is Judges of the United States District Court for the District of New Jersey."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information related to Guy Leverne, his fake works, or the subject matter concerning Judges of the United States District Court for the District of New Jersey. Therefore, the triple is incorrect based on the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "None of the provided news articles mention Guy Leverne Fake or any work related to Judges of the United States District Court for the District of New Jersey.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information does not provide any information about Guy Leverne Fake or their work, and the provided text appears to be a collection of news articles and court cases related to various individuals and topics, with no connection to a specific artist or their subject matter.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention or reference any work by a subject named Guy Leverne Fake, nor does it contain any details about Judges of the United States District Court for the District of New Jersey. The content focuses on various criminal cases and charges in New Jersey without connecting to the specified claim.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}